&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，我们来看看另一个例子。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right, we're
gonna take a look at another example.
我要进去，关闭活动监控器。
Gonna go into that,
close activity monitor.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我只是要做一个MPM开始。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I'm just
gonna do an MPM start.
我得到了服务器作为这个很酷的端口名称。
I got the server as this cool port name.
我们会继续我们会带它去兜风。
We'll go ahead we'll take it for a spin.
我们将使用布局乐趣。
We're going to use layout fun.
因为这就是我们现在谈论的。
Because that's what we're
talking about right now.
好的，这是一个动画。
All right so here's an animation.
你可以看到它相当简陋。
And you can see it's pretty janky.
对，那不是流畅的动画。
Right, that's not a fluid animation.
事情有点结巴。
Things are kind of stuttering.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：让我们来看看我们的工具。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Let's go ahead and
take a look at our tools.
我们来录音吧。
Let's do a recording.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：你知道，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And you know,
这是更加简陋的，因为记录的过程需要大量的带宽。
this is even more janky cuz the process
of recording takes a lot of bandwidth.
就像我之前说的，测量的行为会让事情变得更糟。
Like I said before,
the act of measuring makes stuff worse.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：尤其是如果你使用的是一台12英寸的小MacBook。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Especially if you're
on a little twelve-inch MacBook.
哇，那不是很好，对吧？
Wow, that's not great, right?
太久了。如果我们走得足够远，
It's taking too long.
If we go in far enough,
你可以看到它是，我们是我们在打击，对吗？
you can see that it is,
we are we're thrashing, right?
我们正在重新计算。我们正在重新计算。
We're recalculating.
这不太好对吧？
This is not good, right?
给定帧花费205毫秒。
A given frame took 205 milliseconds.
用户会注意到的，对吧？
Users are gonna notice that, right?
这将是看起来和感觉为我们janky。
That is going to look and
feel janky for us.
就算你们都在一堆箱子周围飞来飞去，就像完全一样。
Granted you're all flying around
a bunch of boxes, like totally.
酷，所以最大的问题是我们该怎么做，对吧？
Cool, so the big question is
what do we do about it, right?
所以让我们来看一下代码。
So let's take a look at the code.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：进入渲染。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Go into rendering.
我们前进到移动的箱子，我们会看看。
We go ahead to the moving boxes and
we’ll look at.
所以，我有一些我们不需要真正担心的设置代码。
So, I’ve got some setup code that we
don’t have to really worry about.
基本上就是让按钮工作，启动和停止。
It’s basically getting the buttons
working and starting and stopping.
并且，让我们假设它不存在。
And, let’s make believe
that doesn’t exist.
但是，如果你好奇的话，这里就是。
But, here it is in case you were curious.
所以，我们有的是，我们将得到数组中的所有元素。
So, then what we have is we're gonna
get all the elements in array.
然后，你猜对了，我们要读。
And then, you guessed it,
we're going to read.
我们要做一些花哨的数学运算，让它成为动画，所以
We're going to do some fancy pants
math to just make it animatable and so
它通过使用你知道的重现。
that it recurs by using you know.
然后我们要改变他们的CSS转换，对吗？
And then we're going to change
their CSS transformation, right?
正如我们所看到的，这肯定会给我们带来一些问题，对吧？
And as we saw, that is definitely
causing some problems for us, right?
所以很明显，我们可以应用我们上次做的同样的事情，也就是做它
So obviously we could just apply the same
thing we did last time which is do it
分两步，对吧？
in two steps, right?
那会有用的。
That would work.
让我们试一试，看看有什么不同。
Let's try it out see
what the difference is.
酷，所以让我们继续找出每个人的下一个位置。
Cool, so let's go ahead and
figure out each one's next position.
我觉得我的间距有点偏。
I think my spacing's a little off here.
我们会为每个人找出下一个位置。
We'll figure out the next position for
each one.
所以我们说Const NextPositions复数。
So we'll say const nextPositions plural.
我们将采用与上次完全相同的方法。
We'll do exactly the same
approach that we took last time.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我们会继续，我们会在这里解决所有的问题。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We'll go ahead and
we'll figure that all out here.
一点点复制-粘贴动作。
A little bit of copy-paste action.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：这里我们只有const next Position。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
here we'll just have const nextPosition.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，所以我们会继续做大量的阅读，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right, so
we'll go ahead and do a lot of reading,
然后我们会继续做大量的写作。
then we'll go ahead and
do a lot of writing.
让我们看看会发生什么。
And let's see what happens for us.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：酷，所以让我们继续，好多了，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Cool, so
let's go ahead, much better, right?
光滑多了。
Much smoother.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：让我们继续做另一个录音。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Let's go ahead and
do another recording.
还有，你看到我在前一个中对CPU做了什么吗？
Also, do you see what I did to
the CPU in that previous one?
它对我不满意。
It was not happy with me.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：让我们在这里继续。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Let's go ahead in here.
你看，它看起来有点简陋，
You see it looked a little bit jankier,
但是，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们确实需要重新计算
but,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We do need to recalculate
每一帧的风格，我们不会摆脱它，但是
the style for every frame,
we're not getting out of that one, but
我们从200人下降到47人。
we went from 200 down to 47.
另一块冰在屏幕上没有你正在制作动画的那么多方框
The other piece of ice don't have that
many boxes on the screen you're animating
同时。
at the same time.
在这种情况下我们永远都不会进入16号，对吧？
We're never gonna get down to
the 16 in this case, right?
但我们确实削减了80%，这将算作一场胜利。
But we did cut it by 80%
which will count as a win.
当你看到它不是所有的小盒子，对吗？
And when you see it's not all
of those little boxes, right?
好的，这就是我们所期待的。
Okay, that's what we expected.
我们在前面的示例中看到了它。
We saw it in the previous example.
这很酷，但有一个问题。
That's pretty cool but there's a problem.
如果我告诉你不要这么做，你就会说，是的，我不会这么做的。
If I told you not to do this you'd just
be like, yeah, I'm not gonna do it.
还记得我之前在我的应用程序中向您展示的代码吗？
Remember that code I showed you
before in my application, right?
发生了。
It's happening.
不是我干的，我更清楚，对吧？
I didn't do it, I know better, right?
但这显然正在发生。
But it's clearly happening.
因为如果我们把工作做好了，
Because if we're doing our jobs well,
很多时候我们喜欢为不同的关注点分离代码，对吗？
a lot of times we like separating our
code out for different concerns, right?
我们正在努力确保，好吧，这里重要的东西
We're trying to make sure that,
okay, the stuff that matters here
与具有不同关注点的代码分离。
is separated from the code
that has a different concern.
这意味着你可以有一些布局颠覆发生在两个非常
Which means that you could have some
layout thrashing happening from two very
代码库的不同末端。
different ends of your code base.
在那里你看不到一个发生在另一个之前。
Where you don't see one
happening before the other.
但事实证明，他们是，你穿插你的阅读和
But it turns out that they are,
you are interspersing your reading and
你的写作，对吧？
your writing, right?
你甚至不知道，因为它们在两个完全不同的文件中。
You didn't even know it because they're
in two totally different files.
你已经很久没碰过他们了，而且
You haven't touched one
of them in forever, and
很明显发生了，对吧？
it's clearly happening, right?
这就是我如何在我的代码库中使用它。
That's how I had it in my code base.
当我第一次去找例子的时候，
When I first went to go find the example,
我的计划是在项目中执行Cmd+Shift+F，在项目中查找。
my plan was to do a Cmd+Shift +F
in the project, find in project.
搜索一些我知道会有问题的布局属性。
Search for some of the layout properties
that I knew were gonna be problematic.
然后责备某人并取笑他们，对吗？
And then give blame to somebody and
make fun of them, right?
代码中没有您可以看到发生这种情况的示例，对吗？
There was no examples in the code where
you could see that happening, right?
一个接一个但是
One after the other but
很明显，这是因为这些东西只是被分离出来的。
clearly it is because this stuff
was just separated out and out.
好吧，那你能做什么，对吧？
All right, so then what can you do, right?
我们可以尝试一些事情。
We can try some things.
一种是使用requestAnimationFrame。
One would be to use requestAnimationFrame.
RequestAnimationFrame基本上告诉浏览器，嘿，当你准备
RequestAnimationFrame basically tells the
browser, hey, when you're getting ready to
再次渲染，让我给你这个函数。
render something again,
let me give you this function.
你可以继续打电话给它，对吧？
And you can go ahead and call it, right?
但根据定义，那是以后的事，对吧？
But by definition, that is later, right?
所以我们能做的就是我们现在可以在阅读的基础上做到这一点
And so what we can do is we can
do it off our reading now and
然后我们总是可以只是我们可以嘿，
then we can always just we can be hey,
无论何时写入DOM，我都会使用requestAnimationFrame so
whenever am going to write to the DOM I'll
use a requestAnimationFrame so
我知道在运行我所有的代码时，我所有的JaveScript都会读取。
that I know that on this pass of running
all my code all my JaveScripts gonna read.
我知道稍后当所有这些请求AnimationFrames
And I know later when all
those requestAnimationFrames
回到栖息地，所有的文字都将成批处理。
come back to roost all
the writing will be batched.
我的意思是我们可以试一试，让我们看看。
I mean we can give it a shot, let's see.
因此，这将涉及到有效地撤消我们之前所做的更改。
So this will involve effectively
undoing the change we did before.
你可以按Cmd+Z几次？
How many times can you hit Cmd+Z?
好了，现在，我们开始吧。
All right, now, there we go.
酷，所以让我们抓住这部分，我们真正写的地方。
Cool, so let's grab this part
where we actually did the writing.
我们只说requestAnimationFrame。
And we'll just say requestAnimationFrame.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我们会把它放在那里。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
we'll put it in there.
好的，现在我们知道这不会马上发生。
All right, so now we know it's
not gonna happen immediately.
这意味着所有的读操作都会发生，然后所有的写操作都会发生。
Which means all the reads will happen and
then all the writes will happen.
我们会刷新页面，我还不能录音吗？
And we'll refresh the page,
I'm not gonna do recording yet?
看起来很顺利，对吧？
Seems pretty smooth, right?
看起来不错我很喜欢。
Seems good I'm into it.
好的，我们来录音。
All right, let's do a recording.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我可能应该停止这样做。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I should
probably stop that.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以我们在这里得到了这个更大的火焰图表。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
we got this bigger flame chart right here.
部分原因是匿名功能
And part of it is that's
the Anonymous function
来自requestAnimationFrame，对吗？
from the requestAnimationFrame, right?
这是框架，使用匿名功能。
Here's the frame, use Anonymous function.
然后我们会去觅食，但看看这个，我们正在计算很多
Then we are gonna forage but
look at that, we are calculating a lot of
requestAnimationFrames因为我们做了一大堆，对吗？
requestAnimationFrames cuz we
are doing it a whole bunch, right?
我们只使用requestAnimationFrame，以使它在以后发生。
We are only using requestAnimationFrame,
to make it happen this thing happen later.
我们不需要这么多动画帧，对吧？
We didn't need these many
animation frames, right?
它实际上是在阻止我们制作动画帧。
It's actually stopping us
from animation framing.
[笑]它阻止我们及时制作动画帧，对吗？
[LAUGH] It's stopping us from making that
frame in time for the animation, right?
比以前的版本好多了，对吧？
It's less bad than the previous version,
right?
这取决于你是乐观主义者还是悲观主义者。
Twice as better of half as bad depending
on if you are an optimist or pessimist.
但这肯定不好，因为我们正在做很多重复的工作。
But it's certainly not good because
we are doing a lot of repeated work.
这并不是很好。
And that's not great.